<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NoStallinApp</string>
    <string name="google_place_api">AIzaSyAp3pmCiv9WGuMHMDvdLkKft-gfeU5rts4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome!</string>
    <string name="welcome_description">Many Bathrooms designated for use by “men” lack individual stalls or have no doors- how about a moment of privacy, folks? \nNo Stallin’ is here to help: This app can help you know or share: Does that men’s room have a stall? Does the stall have a door?!\nUse it before you go out to help you plan! Add data about a place you’ve been to help those who come after.\nYou can add information about known locations and investigate new ones. <b>We use crowd-sourced data - Help us gather reliable Intel!</b> Quit Stallin’ and start No Stallin’! </string>
    <string name="no_info">UH-OH-NO INFO !!  CAN YOU HELP ??</string>
    <string name="maps_description">Thanks for helping us map more stalls!! \n 1. Tap the information window on map pin to add data \n 2. Answer as many of the questions as you can  \n 3. Hit Save! \n You can always come back and edit your locations at a later date.</string>
    <string name="about"><b> L. Zachary DuBois, Ph.d.: Designer and Project leader.</b>\nCurrently an Assistant Professor of Anthropology at California State University Long Beach (CSULB), he is an out transgender man who designed and conducted the Trans Experience Study (TEST). He learned from 65 trans masculine men some of the challenges faced during gender transition, which inspired the creation of this app.\n\n<b>Niyati Shah, B.SC.: App Developer and Tech Super Star!</b>\nGraduate Master’s student in Computer Science at CSULB, she has worked as a Software Consultant and is currently conducting research on Machine Learning. Her skills made this happen.\n\n<b>Judith Moman, JD,: Project And App Release Manager.</b>\n Attorney and advocate on a host of LGBTQ issues including family law, name and gender changes, youth mentorship, and estate planning. Self appointed global bathroom critic and waste management zealot.\n\n<b>Further project assistance:</b> CSULB undergraduate RA’s: Phoenix Pedro, Tian Walker anf Jayvian McNeill.\n\n<b>Critical Design Support:</b> Antonia Clifford, Northwestern University\n<b>More Tech Backup:</b>Lukas Blakk, TechButch</string>
    <string name="faq"><b>What does this app do? </b>No Stallin exclusively helps you learn if there is a stall with a door in a Men’s rooms at locations with user generated data. No Stallin does not assess safety of any restroom. It is based on your input – built up and maintained by you. \n \n <b>Why make this app?</b>  The idea for this app came out of the Trans Experience Study (TEST) in which 65 trans masculine men were interviewed about challenges they faced during their transition. Many (understandably) described how stressful they found using gender-specific  public men’s rooms to be. We want to help. \n \n <b>Why Only Men’s Rooms?</b>  Many public Men’s rooms don’t have stalls with working doors in them. Many have urinals against the wall and then a toilet in a corner with a wall barrier but no stall with a door.  If you do not, or cannot, use a urinal, this can mean there is no place for you to go to the bathroom. For those who use women’s rooms – stall doors tend not to be the issue. \n \n <b>Why not use Restroom Refuge?</b> DO use Restroom Refuge! Restroom Refuge can help you find a safe, single-use gender neutral restroom! But it can’t help you find out if there is a stall with a door in a men’s room that is for multi-person use. \n \n <b>So this app is only for trans men?</b> Nope. Of course not silly. This app is for anyone who has the pleasure of using men’s rooms. Have fun. Everyone needs to use a bathroom. This app is a tool to help anyone who uses Men’s rooms. Either help plan ahead BEFORE you are there or reporting to the global Men’s bathroom using community where a quiet stall can be found! </string>
    <string name="contact"><b><u>Email:</u></b> nostallinapp@gmail.com</string>

</resources>
